Victor Pinacue- Bibby Curriculum Vitae

Mobile: 0426939417 Email: victor.pinacue@gmail.com

Business Website: <u>cryptoinvestor.tech</u>

About Me.

I've pursued various occupations and gotten good at various tasks along my journey, I keep pushing to achieve higher goals and test the limits of my innate capacity. I have a wide range of interests from philosophy, reading, tech and health. I'm developing my coding skills by taking courses online via Freecodecamp. I have an interest in tech start-ups and thinking outside of the box to provide solutions to real-world problems. I founded my first Crypto news business in October 2023 which focuses on short-form articles which educate people on various ways to make money with crypto. My goal is to build my experience with building businesses and scaling them.

Employment History:

2023 - 2024 November - January

• Wrote a Book - We are made of the stars

A Philosphical book on Love, life and the matrix we exist in, the reality we have to endure.

2023 October - Present

• Founder - Crypto Investor

Business website - Cryptoinvestor.tech

Designed and developed with HTML, CSS and Javascript written by me. All short crypto articles are written by me, and more to come in the future by other crypto writers. The aim is to educate and show people how they can make great returns ranging from 2 - 3% daily through various crypto investing platforms, to create a new generation of crypto millionaires.

2023 February - September

Energy Consultant at Empower Solar Australia

Calling warm leads, building rapport, assessing energy consumption needs, designing bespoke solar systems using Pylon, and educating the client on the benefits of renewable energy and what are the leading products on the market.

2022 June - December

Sales Agent at Aurenew Energy

Appointment setting D2D, talking to customers about solar and the benefits of reducing their energy bill through solar installation and offering them no deposit interest free finance. Admin duties such as tracking leads on Excel. Closing leads efficiently.

2022 July - September

Glass collector at the Old Synagogue

In charge of collecting glasses and clearing tables throughout the venue and at times working the bar back with the duty of sorting through glassware, washing it and storing them in the required spots.

2021 - 2022 Feb

Retail Associate at Oakley DFO (Luxottica group)

Reporting directly to the Store Manager, involves working alongside the team to achieve monthly budgeted sales, maintaining stock levels and store presentation and driving sales by creating unique customer experiences through great communication and a high level of assertiveness.

2021

• Certificate III in Process Manufacturing (Focused on warehouse operations)

The MSM30116 Certificate III in Process Manufacturing provides the competencies required by advanced production workers who use a range of equipment and provide support functions directly related to producing products. To undertake more advanced roles. Working in accordance with operating procedures and applying knowledge to anticipate problems and solve a range of foreseen and unforeseen problems.

2019

Simply Energy: Sales Representative.

Cold calling on potential customers with the intention to help them with regards to the outgoing gas bills. To work on the go by using iPad, Microsoft Word and Excel which enabled me to keep track of the status of sales and customers.

2019

• Stellar Asia Pacific: Customer Service Specialist.

Taking incoming calls from prospective customers and distributing them to the appropriate department. Solving phone queries for customers. Emailing customers and other employees to inform them of issues that may be arising. Competent at Microsoft Word and Excel.

2017-2018

• CJS Projects (WA) Pty Ltd: Trade Assistant. Employed by an essential contractor with regards to fully constructing two full schools. To help fit out a hospital unit to the high standards that is required of the West Australian Health Service.

2016

• Self-employed contractor: (ABN Registered business)

In charge of waitering to my designated area with regards to duties of Pouring drinks, serving food and making sure that the client has an excellent experience of dining.

2013 - 2016

• Skill Hire: Apprentice Roof Carpenter.

Use of electrical equipment to the OHS safety standards including the use of PPE. Such jobs would be Cutting timber to specific sizes, building from scratch stud wall's and making sure that they are square and to drawings, Ceiling installation with regards to levelling and preparation of equipment. Installation of roofs and Decking.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

- 2021 First Aid and CPR
- 2021 Certificate III in Process Manufacturing (Focused on warehouse operations)
- 2017 Diploma of Property Services (Agency Management)
- 2015 RSA
- 2014 Certificate II Carpentry and Joinery
- 2013 White Card Silver Trowel, WA
- Driver's Licence (C-A)
- FreeCodeCamp Front end responsive design / Data structures and Algorithms
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, NextJS, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS

PROJECTS - WEBSITES I HAVE CREATED

- https://victorpinacue.webflow.io/
- https://victors-marvelous-site-aurenew-energy-f.webflow.io/
- https://cryptoinvestor.tech/

References

Don Xu

CEO Founder - Empower Solar Australia 0412313285

Anthony Lentini

National Sales Manager - Empower Solar Australia 04018555015

Joshua Lim

Senior Energy Consultant - Empower Solar Australia 043243967

Jordan Todd

Store Manager - Oakley DFO 0414941457

Chris Riby

Director - CJS Projects (WA) Pty Ltd 0455152695

Matthew Prior

Sales agent manager – Aurenew Energy 0472600406

Prof. Ismail Ahmed MD

Life coach - Envision your life 0412302078